Inventory of the Francis E. Warren Papers, 1867-1974
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
- Series II. Personal Papers, 1868-1974
  - Subseries 2. Fred E. Warren Correspondence, 1903-1949; 2.25 cubic ft. (3 document boxes, 6 letterbooks).
    - Subsubseries 2. General Correspondence, 1913-1946
      - O, P, 1914-1930; microfilm reel 176 (Box 59, Folder 2)
      - R, 1913-1930; microfilm reel 176 (Box 59, Folder 3)
      - Sons Of The American Revolution, 1917-1946; microfilm reel 176 (Box 59, Folder 4)
      - S, T, 1909-1928; microfilm reel 176 (Box 59, Folder 5)
      - U-W, 1908-1930; microfilm reel 176 (Box 59, Folder 6)
      - Wyoming Wool Growers Association-Z, 1916-1930; microfilm reel 176 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Subsubseries 3. Personal Correspondence, 1913-1936
      - John J. Pershing and Family, 1914-1928; microfilm reel 177 (Box 60, Folder 1)
      - Eliza and H. E. Stanton, 1913-1930; microfilm reel 177 (Box 60, Folder 2)
      - Warren Family, 1913-1930; microfilm reel 177 (Box 60, Folder 3)
      - Clara Warren, 1927-1931; microfilm reel 177 (Box 60, Folder 4)
      - Leona M. Wells, 1923-1930; microfilm reel 177 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 3. Financial and Legal Records, 1871-1949; 5.5 cubic ft. (5 document boxes, 25 books).
    Included are tax returns, estate and will papers, deeds, mortgages, ledgers, journals, bills and receipts. This series is divided into 8 subseries:
    - Warren Income Tax Returns, 1918-1936; Subsubseries 1.
      - F. E. Warren Income Tax Returns, 1918-1922; microfilm reel 178 (Box 61, Folder 1)
      - F. E. Warren Income Tax Returns, 1923-1929; microfilm reel 178 (Box 61, Folder 2)
      - F. E. Warren Claim for Tax Refund, 1920; microfilm reel 178 (Box 61, Folder 3)
      - Clara Warren Income Tax Returns, 1930-1936; microfilm reel 178 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Subsubseries 2. Family Estate and Wills, 1876-1942
      - F. E. Warren Estate Papers, 1876-1929; microfilm reel 179 (Box 62, Folder 1)
      - F. E. Warren Wills and Correspondence, 1917,1919; microfilm reel 179 (Box 62, Folder 2)
      - F. E. Warren Last Will, Estate Papers, 1929-1930; microfilm reel 179 (Box 62, Folder 3)
      - F. E. Warren Estate Taxes, 1929-1934; microfilm reel 179 (Box 62, Folder 4)
      - F. E. Warren Estate Tax Papers, 1931-1932; microfilm reel 179 (Box 62, Folder 5)
      - F. E. Warren Life Insurance, 1929; microfilm reel 179 (Box 62, Folder 6)
      - Frances W. Pershing Estate, 1918; microfilm reel 179 (Box 62, Folder 7)
      - Clara Warren Russell Will and Estate, 1941-1942; microfilm reel 179 (Box 62, Folder 8)
      - Susan g. Morgan Estate, 1922; microfilm reel 179 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Subsubseries 3. Legal Documents, Deeds and Mortgages, 1871-1922
      - H. Glafcke Quick Claim Deed, 1871; microfilm reel 180 (Box 63, Folder 1)
      - H. Glafcke Mortgage Deed, 1876; microfilm reel 180 (Box 63, Folder 2)
      - Glafcke, Collins, Nagle, Uprr Warranty Deeds, 1881-1894; microfilm reel 180 (Box 63, Folder 3)
      - Abstracts of Titles and Taxes, 1883,1890,1894; microfilm reel 180 (Box 63, Folder 4)
      - Agreements, 1885,1889; microfilm reel 180 (Box 63, Folder 5)
      - Report of Fraudulent Claim or Entry, 1889; microfilm reel 180 (Box 63, Folder 6)
      - Silver Crown Mining Report, 1897; microfilm reel 180 (Box 63, Folder 7)
      - Taylor Escrow Agreement, 1906; microfilm reel 180 (Box 63, Folder 8)
      - Stocks, 1874-1914; microfilm reel 180 (Box 63, Folder 9)
      - Warren Family Legal Documents, Deeds and Mortgages, 1870s; microfilm reel 180 (Box 64, Folder 1)
      - Warren Family Legal Documents, Deeds and Mortgages, 1880s; microfilm reel 180 (Box 64, Folder 2)
      - Warren Family Legal Documents, Deeds and Mortgages, 1890s; microfilm reel 180 (Box 64, Folder 3)
      - Warren Family Legal Documents, Deeds and Mortgages, 1900-1904; microfilm reel 180 (Box 64, Folder 4)
      - Warren Family Legal Documents, Deeds and Mortgages, 1905-1909; microfilm reel 180 (Box 64, Folder 5)
      - Warren Family Legal Documents, Deeds and Mortgages, 1910-1914; microfilm reel 180 (Box 64, Folder 6)
      - Warren Family Legal Documents, Deeds and Mortgages, 1915-1922; microfilm reel 180 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Subsubseries 4. Francis E. Warren Financial Books, 1881-1932
      - Ledger, 1881-1889; microfilm reel 181 (Box 65, Folder 1)
      - Journal, 1881-1885; microfilm reel 181 (Box 66, Folder 1)
      - Journal, 1887-1889; microfilm reel 181 (Box 67, Folder 1)
      - Journal, 1889-1892; microfilm reel 181 (Box 68, Folder 1)
      - Journal, 1901-1908; microfilm reel 182 (Box 69, Folder 1)
      - Journal, 1909-1920; microfilm reel 182 (Box 70, Folder 1)
      - Journal, 1911-1917; microfilm reel 182 (Box 71, Folder 1)
      - Ledger, 1914-1929; microfilm reel 183 (Box 72, Folder 1)
      - Journal, 1920-1927; microfilm reel 183 (Box 73, Folder 1)
      - Journal, 1927-1930; microfilm reel 183 (Box 74, Folder 1)
      - Estate Trial Balance, 1929-1932; microfilm reel 183 (Box 75, Folder 1)
      - Estate Ledger, 1929-1931; microfilm reel 183 (Box 76, Folder 1)
      - Estate Journal, 1929-1931; microfilm reel 183 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Subsubseries 5. Fred E. Warren Financial Books, 1902-1949
      - Daybook, 1902-1909; microfilm reel 184 (Box 78, Folder 1)
      - Ledger, 1902-1909; microfilm reel 184 (Box 78, Folder 2)
      - Ledger, 1909-1929; microfilm reel 184 (Box 78, Folder 3)
      - Journal, 1920-1931; microfilm reel 184 (Box 78, Folder 4)
      - Ledger, 1929-1941; microfilm reel 184 (Box 78, Folder 5)
      - Journal, 1931-1941; microfilm reel 184 (Box 78, Folder 6)
      - Journal, 1947-1949; microfilm reel 184 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Subsubseries 6. Francis E. Warren Receipts, Letterheads, 1876-1923
      - A, B, C, 1882-1923; microfilm reel 185 (Box 79, Folder 1)
      - C-G, 1883-1923; microfilm reel 185 (Box 79, Folder 2)
      - H-K, 1879-1912; microfilm reel 185 (Box 79, Folder 3)
      - L-M, 1885-1914; microfilm reel 185 (Box 79, Folder 4)
      - N-P, R, 1883-1914; microfilm reel 185 (Box 79, Folder 5)
      - S-V, 1876-1913; microfilm reel 185 (Box 79, Folder 6)
      - W, Z, 1882-1919; microfilm reel 185 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Subsubseries 7. Francis E. Warren Private Bills and Receipts, 1877-1880
      - Private Bills and Receipts, 1876-1879; microfilm reel 186 (Box 80, Folder 1)
      - Private Bills and Receipts, 1879-1880; microfilm reel 186 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Subsubseries 8. Fred E. Warren Receipts, 1913-1931
      - Receipts, 1913-1931; microfilm reel 187 (Box 81, Folder 1)
      - Receipts, 1917-1931; microfilm reel 187 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 4. Scrapbooks, 1896-1922; 2.5 cubic ft. (10 books).
    8 invitational scrapbooks are arranged chronologically, 1 scrapbook deals with the death of Frances (Warren) Pershing and her three daughters, the Pershing Memorial Hospital and John J. Pershing's career. One scrapbook is news clippings concerning the railroad in 1909. This series is divided into 3 subseries:
    - Subsubseries 1. Invitations, 1896-1912
      - Scrapbook, 1901-1906; microfilm reel 188 (Box 82, Folder 1)
      - Scrapbook, 1896-1903; microfilm reel 188 (Box 82, Folder 2)
      - Scrapbook, 1903-1904; microfilm reel 188 (Box 82, Folder 3)
      - Scrapbook, 1905-1906; microfilm reel 189 (Box 83, Folder 1)
      - Scrapbook, 1906-1907; microfilm reel 189 (Box 83, Folder 2)
      - Scrapbook, 1907-1908; microfilm reel 189 (Box 83, Folder 3)
      - Scrapbook, 1908-1909; microfilm reel 189 (Box 84, Folder 1)
      - Scrapbook, 1910-1912; microfilm reel 189 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Subsubseries 2. Pershing Family, 1915-1922
      - Scrapbook, 1915-1922; Pershing tragedy, mattress incident Pershing Memorial Hospital, Pershing career; microfilm reel 190 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Subsubseries 3. Railroads, 1909
      - Scrapbook, 1909; newspaper clippings; microfilm reel 190 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 5. Francis E. Warren Miscellaneous Correspondence and Interests, 1867-1928; 7 cubic ft. (2 document boxes).
    Arranged alphabetically. Includes biographies, marriage certificate, Medal of Honor, military pension, family interests, F.E.W. and John J. Pershing newspaper clippings, and a copied letter from Theodore Roosevelt (1910).
    - Francis E. Warren Biographies, n.d.; microfilm reel 191 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Certificate of Marriage, 1871; Francis E. Warren and Helen Smith; microfilm reel 191 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Francis E. Warren Invitations, Greeting Cards, 1883-1908; including T. Roosevelt; microfilm reel 191 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Francis E. Warren Medal of Honor, 1893-1916; microfilm reel 191 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Francis E. Warren Military Pension, 1912-1928; microfilm reel 191 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Phrenological Character Francis E. Warren, 1880; microfilm reel 191 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Poem: "Warren of Wyoming", 1929; microfilm reel 191 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Frances (Warren) Pershing, 1915-1917; microfilm reel 191 (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - John J. Pershing Articles, Legal Proceedings, 1908-1928; microfilm reel 191 (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - Theodore Roosevelt Letter (Copy) to Francis E. Warren, 1910; microfilm reel 191 (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - Studebaker Car Acquisition, 1908-1909; microfilm reel 191 (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - Cynthia (Abbott) Warren Memorial, 1859; microfilm reel 191 (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - Helen Warren, 1881,1900; microfilm reel 191 (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - Francis E. Warren Newspaper Clippings, 1906-1929; microfilm reel 191 (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - Fort Russell, n.d.; microfilm reel 191 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Frontier Days, 1905-1907; microfilm reel 191 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Signatures, n.d.; microfilm reel 191 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Spanish American War Reports, 1899; microfilm reel 191 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous, 1867-1925; Certificate of Membership, White House, Susan Snyder, Transmitting Drafts, U.S. Treasury, Extracts Francis E. Warren Journal; microfilm reel 191 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Personal, 1928; microfilm reel 191 (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - Clippings, 1929,n.d.; microfilm reel 191 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Subseries 6. Photographs, Negatives and Steel Plates, 1871-1974; .45 cubic ft. (1 document box).
    Arranged alphabetically. Includes Bantayan Islands with letter from King Harry N. McLauley, Theodore Roosevelt, San Francisco, Helen (Smith) Warren, Mary Helen Warren, steel plate portraits of F.E.W. and his funeral, unidentified photographs and photograph negatives from Warren Live Stock Company.
    - Bantayan Islands, 1902; microfilm reel 192 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Theodore Roosevelt, 1903,1910; microfilm reel 192 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - San Francisco, 1902; microfilm reel 192 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Helen (Smith) Warren, 1871; microfilm reel 192 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Mary Helen Warren, n.d.; microfilm reel 192 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Unidentified, n.d.; microfilm reel 192 (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Francis E. Warren, n.d.; microfilm reel 192 (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Francis E. Warren, 1926; microfilm reel 192 (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - Francis E. Warren, 1929; microfilm reel 192 (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - Warren Live Stock Company, 1974; microfilm reel 192 (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 7. Francis E. Warren II Correspondence, 1938-1949; .17 cubic ft. (1 letterbook).
    General and personal correspondence.
    - Letterbook, 1938-1949; microfilm reel 193 (Box 88, Folder 1)
- Series III. Warren Live Stock Company, 1882-1957
  - Subseries 1. Letters, 1882-1930; 5.7 cubic ft. (14 document boxes)
    Arranged chronologically by year and alphabetically by company or personal name of the signer. Contains correspondence concerning the daily operation of Warren Live Stock. Includes telegrams and letters dealing with the federal, state, and local authorities as well as businesses nationwide whose services were necessary to operating a livestock company. Includes telegrams and correspondence from F.E. Warren.
    - Letters 1892, 1897-1899
    - A-Z, 1892; microfilm reel 194 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - A-Z, 1897; microfilm reel 194 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - A-Z, 1898; microfilm reel 194 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - A-B, 1899; microfilm reel 194 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - C-D, 1899; microfilm reel 194 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - E-F, 1899; microfilm reel 194 (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - G-H, 1899; microfilm reel 194 (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - I-J, 1899; microfilm reel 194 (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - K-L, 1899; microfilm reel 194 (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - M-N, 1899; microfilm reel 194 (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - O-P, 1899; microfilm reel 194 (Box 89, Folder 11)
    - Q-R, 1899; microfilm reel 194 (Box 89, Folder 12)
    - S-T, 1899; microfilm reel 194 (Box 89, Folder 13)
    - U-V, 1899; microfilm reel 194 (Box 89, Folder 14)
    - W-X, 1899; microfilm reel 194 (Box 89, Folder 15)
    - Y-Z, 1899; microfilm reel 194 (Box 89, Folder 16)
    - Letters, 1900-1902
    - A, microfilm reel 194 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - B, microfilm reel 194 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - C, microfilm reel 194 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - D, microfilm reel 194 (Box 90, Folder 4-5)
    - E, microfilm reel 194 (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - F, microfilm reel 194 (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - G, microfilm reel 194 (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - H, microfilm reel 194 (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - H, microfilm reel 195 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - I-J, microfilm reel 195 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - K, microfilm reel 195 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - L, microfilm reel 195 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - M, microfilm reel 195 (Box 91, Folder 5-6)
    - N, microfilm reel 195 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - O, microfilm reel 195 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - P-Q, microfilm reel 195 (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - R, microfilm reel 195 (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - S, microfilm reel 195 (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - T, microfilm reel 196 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - U-V, microfilm reel 196 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - W, microfilm reel 196 (Box 92, Folder 3-5)
    - X-Z, microfilm reel 196 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - A, microfilm reel 196 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - B, microfilm reel 196 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - C, microfilm reel 196 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - D, microfilm reel 196 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - E, microfilm reel 196 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - F, microfilm reel 196 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - G, microfilm reel 196 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - H, microfilm reel 196 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - I-J, microfilm reel 196 (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - K, microfilm reel 196 (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - L, microfilm reel 196 (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - M, microfilm reel 196 (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - N-O, microfilm reel 196 (Box 93, Folder 13)
    - P-Q, microfilm reel 196 (Box 93, Folder 14)
    - R, microfilm reel 196 (Box 93, Folder 15)
    - S, microfilm reel 196 (Box 93, Folder 16)
    - T, microfilm reel 196 (Box 93, Folder 17)
    - U-V, microfilm reel 196 (Box 93, Folder 18)
    - W, microfilm reel 196 (Box 93, Folder 19)
    - X-Z, microfilm reel 196 (Box 93, Folder 20)
    - Letters, 1903-1904
    - A, microfilm reel 197 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - B, microfilm reel 197 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - C, microfilm reel 197 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - D, microfilm reel 197 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - E, microfilm reel 197 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - F, microfilm reel 197 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - G, microfilm reel 197 (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - H, microfilm reel 197 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - I-J, microfilm reel 197 (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - K, microfilm reel 197 (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - L, microfilm reel 197 (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - M, microfilm reel 197 (Box 94, Folder 12)
    - N-O, microfilm reel 197 (Box 94, Folder 13)
    - P-Q, microfilm reel 197 (Box 94, Folder 14)
    - R, microfilm reel 197 (Box 94, Folder 15)
    - S, microfilm reel 197 (Box 94, Folder 16)
    - T, microfilm reel 197 (Box 94, Folder 17)
    - U-V, microfilm reel 197 (Box 94, Folder 18)
    - W, microfilm reel 197 (Box 94, Folder 19)
    - X-Z, microfilm reel 197 (Box 94, Folder 20)
    - Letters, 1904-1905
    - A, microfilm reel 197 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - B, microfilm reel 197 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - C-D, microfilm reel 198 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - E-F, microfilm reel 198 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - G, microfilm reel 198 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - H-J, microfilm reel 198 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - K-L, microfilm reel 198 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - M, microfilm reel 198 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - N-P, microfilm reel 198 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Q-R, microfilm reel 198 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - S, microfilm reel 199 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - T-V, microfilm reel 199 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - W, microfilm reel 199 (Box 96, Folder 6-7)
    - X-Z, microfilm reel 199 (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Letters, 1906-1907
    - A, microfilm reel 199 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - B, microfilm reel 199 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - C, microfilm reel 199 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - D, microfilm reel 199 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - E, microfilm reel 199 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - F, microfilm reel 200 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - G, microfilm reel 200 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - H, microfilm reel 200 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - I, microfilm reel 200 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - J, microfilm reel 200 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - K, microfilm reel 200 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - L, microfilm reel 200 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - M, microfilm reel 200 (Box 98, Folder 6-7)
    - N, microfilm reel 200 (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - O, microfilm reel 200 (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - P-Q, microfilm reel 200 (Box 98, Folder 10)
    - R, microfilm reel 200 (Box 98, Folder 11)
    - S, microfilm reel 200 (Box 98, Folder 12)
    - T, microfilm reel 200 (Box 98, Folder 13)
    - U, microfilm reel 201 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - V, microfilm reel 201 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - W, microfilm reel 201 (Box 99, Folder 3-7)
    - X-Z, microfilm reel 201 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Letters, 1907-1908
    - A, microfilm reel 201 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - B, microfilm reel 201 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - C, microfilm reel 201 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - D, microfilm reel 201 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - E, microfilm reel 201 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - F, microfilm reel 201 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - G, microfilm reel 201 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - H, microfilm reel 201 (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - I, microfilm reel 201 (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - J, microfilm reel 201 (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - K, microfilm reel 201 (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - L, microfilm reel 201 (Box 100, Folder 12)
    - M, microfilm reel 201 (Box 100, Folder 13)
    - N, microfilm reel 201 (Box 100, Folder 14)
    - O, microfilm reel 201 (Box 100, Folder 15)
    - P-Q, microfilm reel 201 (Box 100, Folder 16)
    - R, microfilm reel 201 (Box 100, Folder 17)
    - S, microfilm reel 201 (Box 100, Folder 18)
    - T, microfilm reel 201 (Box 100, Folder 19)
    - U, microfilm reel 201 (Box 100, Folder 20)
    - V, microfilm reel 201 (Box 100, Folder 21)
    - W, microfilm reel 201 (Box 100, Folder 22)
    - X-Z, microfilm reel 201 (Box 100, Folder 23)
    - Letters, 1908-1910
    - A, microfilm reel 202 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - B, microfilm reel 202 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - C, microfilm reel 202 (Box 101, Folder 3-4)
    - D, microfilm reel 202 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - E, microfilm reel 202 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - F, microfilm reel 202 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - G, microfilm reel 202 (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - H, microfilm reel 202 (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - I-J, microfilm reel 202 (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - K-L, microfilm reel 202 (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - M, microfilm reel 202 (Box 101, Folder 12)
    - N-O, microfilm reel 202 (Box 101, Folder 13)
    - P-Q, microfilm reel 202 (Box 101, Folder 14)
    - R, microfilm reel 202 (Box 101, Folder 15)
    - S, microfilm reel 202 (Box 101, Folder 16)
    - T, microfilm reel 202 (Box 101, Folder 17)
    - U-V, microfilm reel 202 (Box 101, Folder 18)
    - W, microfilm reel 202 (Box 101, Folder 19)
    - X-Z, microfilm reel 202 (Box 101, Folder 20)
    - Letters, 1911-1915, 1929-1930
    - A, 1911-1915; microfilm reel 202 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - B, 1911-1915; microfilm reel 202 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - C, 1911-1915; microfilm reel 202 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - D, 1911-1915; microfilm reel 202 (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - E, 1911-1915; microfilm reel 202 (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - F, 1911-1915; microfilm reel 202 (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - G, 1911-1915; microfilm reel 202 (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - H, 1911-1915; microfilm reel 202 (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - I-J, 1911-1915; microfilm reel 202 (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - K-L, 1911-1915; microfilm reel 202 (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - M, 1911-1915; microfilm reel 202 (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - N-O, 1911-1915; microfilm reel 202 (Box 102, Folder 12)
    - P-Q, 1911-1915; microfilm reel 202 (Box 102, Folder 13)
    - R, 1911-1915; microfilm reel 202 (Box 102, Folder 14)
    - S, 1911-1915; microfilm reel 202 (Box 102, Folder 15)
    - T, 1911-1915; microfilm reel 202 (Box 102, Folder 16)
    - U-V, 1911-1915; microfilm reel 202 (Box 102, Folder 17)
    - W, 1911-1915; microfilm reel 202 (Box 102, Folder 18)
    - X-Z, 1911-1915; microfilm reel 202 (Box 102, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 1929-1930; microfilm reel 202 (Box 102, Folder 20)
    - Maps of Reservoirs and Water Supply Improvement System for Cheyenne and Fort Russell [Oversized see Box 302] Profit and Loss Chart, n.d.,1884-1929; microfilm reel 202 (Box 102, Folder 21)
    - Press Releases, n.d.; microfilm reel 202 (Box 102, Folder 22)
  - Subseries 2. Federal Government, 1891-1918; 1.6 cubic ft. (4 document boxes)
    Arranged chronologically by year and alphabetically by agency or personal name of signer. Contains legal documents, statements, and correspondence regarding the dealings of Warren Live Stock with the federal government, including documentation of Warren's defense against federal allegations of illegal enclosure of public lands in 1906. This series is divided into 2 subseries:
    - Subsubseries 1. Land Fraud Scandal, 1891-1912
      - Correspondence Regarding Conduct of M. A. Meyendorff, 1899; microfilm reel 203 (Box 103, Folder 1)
      - U.S. Department of Justice Correspondence, 1901; microfilm reel 203 (Box 103, Folder 2)
      - Report on U.S. General Land Office Activities, 1889-1906; microfilm reel 203 (Box 103, Folder 3)
      - U.S. Treasury Department Correspondence, 1893-1906; microfilm reel 203 (Box 103, Folder 4)
      - Warren, J. A. Breckons (Warren's Secretary) to Horton Pope, Esq., 1904; microfilm reel 203 (Box 103, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence F. E. Warren to Meyendorff, 1904-1906; microfilm reel 203 (Box 103, Folder 6)
      - M. A. Meyendorff's Suicide Attempt, 1904; microfilm reel 203 (Box 103, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence J. A. Breckons (Warren's Secretary) to the Republican Newspaper, 1906; microfilm reel 203 (Box 103, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence From Republican National Committee, Blue Cap Mining and Milling Company, Thomas Sturgis, Elmer Dover, N. K. Griggs, Dyer O. Clark, 1906; microfilm reel 203 (Box 103, Folder 9)
      - Press Release, 1906; microfilm reel 203 (Box 103, Folder 10)
      - U.S. Department of the Interior, General Land Office, 1906; correspondence, reports; microfilm reel 203 (Box 103, Folder 11)
      - Newspaper Clippings, Correspondence, 1906,1907; microfilm reel 203 (Box 103, Folder 12)
      - Unidentified Speech or Report, n.d.; microfilm reel 203 (Box 103, Folder 13)
      - Court Cases Involving Land Enclosures, Land Disputes Etc. [1891-1908], 1891-1912; microfilm reel 203 (Box 104, Folder 1)
      - Court Cases Involving Enclosures, Land Disputes, Etc. [1908-1912], 1891-1912; microfilm reel 203 (Box 104, Folder 2)
      - House of Representatives, Reports on F. E. W. Enclosure Charges, 1913; microfilm reel 203 (Box 104, Folder 3)
      - U.S. House Committee Brief on F. E. W. Enclosure Charges, n.d.; microfilm reel 203 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Subsubseries 2. Fencing Cases, 1905-1912
      - Fencing Cases, 1906-1910; microfilm reel 204 (Box 105, Folder 1)